Well, uh,
to start as we're hitting here today,
Nick and Julian, you know, would go to
battle and then let's see what, you
know, the next, you know, time during
this off season into the next, you know,
month or so go. But that's where we'll
start.
>> You said,
>> yes.
>> Um, how surprised were you that you guys
got Chris Paul back?
Uh what's your thought at that spot now?
>> Thankful, you know, more so than
surprised. Uh
>> I love seeing Chris get the moment and
just hanging on to it, man. And so he
really uh made an impact as a pass
protector. And so to have, you know, LT
right next to him, some of the, you
know, the protections, their
communication, it was good to see those
two in that way. like when a game
happened, Chris had such strength that
he could move a guy over to LT he could
pick him up. And so those were just a
few of the things to go. And so, uh,
when he came back into the building last
week, it was a good deal, Ben, for us to
see how many people, you know, were that
pumped about it. But that type of rare
size, uh, his length as a pass
protector, um, that was a big deal for
us.
>> Yeah, you guys sort of remade the
quarterback group at Nique and
Witherspoon and losing a couple guys.
How do you feel about where that group
stands now?
>> So adding Spoon just the other day that
was good. So different sizes, different,
you know, ways there's, you know, with
Spoon, the experience with the Meek, and
I'm sure you guys watched it too. The
thing that just absolutely impressed me
before he was a commander was like this
relentless competitive play style. Like
he is an absolute dog. And so those are
the types of competitors I was talking
about. when you add that to the room at
different spots in different areas and
you see things get elevated. Um he'd
already had some previous connection
like with a few of the players here u
with his background from Louisiana and
so um to add him chip on your shoulder
ready to go battle for it. I thought
that's us you know in terms of an
attitude and an edge and I hope that's
what you see you know from us again. And
I thought our first year prior to you
arriving, there was some things that we
liked and then 25 absolutely got punched
in the mouth. And so players like Aik
have the type of resilience and attitude
to battle that I really like. And I'm
very much looking forward to having him
as part of this group. It doesn't just
make just the quarterbacks better. It's
also the receivers and the way that you
practice and the way that you go. And so
all of that when you put into this
competitive arena just elevates. And so
I'm really pumped about him being here.
>> Uh quickly, uh he's a guy that's played
nickel and outside in the past. Do you
have a set spot for him?
>> I don't know yet. Um cuz Mike has also
and so u we'll certainly work them both
at both locations and we'll take some
time to figure that out and what that
looks like. Um, so I'm not sure yet, but
um,
we don't have to today, but um, as we go
through the spring and probably the
first month of camp, you know, we this
day, that day, and then we'll get closer
to how we want to line it all.
>> This might this might be better for
Adam. I don't know, but you see what
happens with the Max Crosby situation
Baltimore. Is there anything that can be
done from a league perspective that can
maybe avoid that situation in the
future, whether it's how, you know, the
physical process, whatever it is.
That's a great one
>> because it is pending the physical and I
don't know if there's a better way that
they could do that. Um
because you wouldn't bring you know the
medical people to somewhere else. The
only thing I can say is that maybe you
do that before. I don't know. I don't
know if there's a better way. It doesn't
happen a lot,
>> right?
>> But when it does um there's a reason
behind it. Not all of the teams
medically grade in the exact same way
either. um one team's grade might have
been okay and another team's grade may
not have been. I had been a part of a um
offseason like that when I was with the
Miami Dolphins and um with a quarterback
and so
didn't have the physical and didn't make
it and the guy went on to have a nice
career.
>> Look at Drew Brees.
>> Yeah. Not figured that out.
>> Yeah. Well, more than nice.
>> Look at how a linebacker with Leo Chanel
between he and Frankie Luvu. Does that
kind of get your defensive mind excited
about kind of the different things you
can do with him?
>> Yeah, because
sometimes Frankie, okay, when it's hard
to just put a back onto him and so a
line could slide that way and you have
to be more creative to bring someone
else to try and find the matchups on the
backs and so by adding Leo into that
who's like an excellent blitzer in his
own right, I thought these are the
matchups that you look for like between
Luvu and Chanel. These are like two very
physical players and so yeah that was
definitely part of the thought process.
>> Last one last one with regard to David
Bla's new setup. Does that change type
of player you want say at offensive
lineman or in other positions?
>> Not as much at offensive line for sure.
At receiver um we were having a
conversation earlier about you know what
an X is or a Z or Y in a slot. So that
part we did have more conversations on
but not with the interior of the line.
>> Can I I didn't expect
>> the Nikki rule. Yeah, we got
>> used to be the kind rule but 2026
>> somebody's going to take on
>> we'll rotate it
>> with Jaden just transition to however
it's just more under center.
>> Yeah.
>> What kind of transition is that Michael?
>> Well I think it's footwork and so that's
where it can start. Um because the drops
could be different when you're in the
gun like a fivestep would be a three.
And so how do you transfer those ones in
the speed of getting out the speed of
getting your play fakes to going? So
that's what he's been working really
hard on as well. So Jane's an accurate
thrower. He's got a big arm and so now
doing some of that setup pitch throw,
you know, quick five. And so the
footwork timing is the biggest I would
say adjustment for it. And then from a
nonphysical
standpoint, um when you huddle a little
more, um cadences and checks and things
that you'd use at the line of scrimmage.
So those would be two points of emphasis
prior to him getting here with the guys.
>> Can I ask?
>> Sure. I was like, "Oh, yeah. You're
out." All right. Okay. you guys travel
safe back and I'll see uh